<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MIT OCW</string>
    <string name="urlExtra">urlExtra</string>
    <string name="courseTitlePlaceholder">Course Title</string>
    <string name="courseDesc">Description</string>
    <string name="courseInstructor">Instructor</string>

    <string name="bookmarks">bookmarks</string>

    <string name="chalkRadio">Chalk Radio</string>
    <string name="listenOn">Listen On</string>
    <string name="chalkRadioDesc">Chalk Radio is an MIT OpenCourseWare podcast about inspired teaching at MIT. They take you behind the scenes of some of the most interesting courses on campus to talk with the professors who make those courses possible. Their guests open up to us about the passions that drive their cutting-edge research and innovative teaching, sharing stories that are candid, funny, serious, personal, and full of insights. Listening in on these conversations is like being right there in person under the MIT dome, talking with your favorite professors. Hosted by Dr. Sarah Hansen. New episode every other Wednesday, starting February 19, 2020.</string>
    <string name="appContribute">Contribute to App</string>
    <string name="appContributeDesc">To be clear, this app is an open sourced unofficial mobile client for MIT OCW. https://ocw.mit.edu/\n\nIf you have any suggestions, feature request or problems, please visit the project on https://github.com/yashx/OCW and tell me about it. I will try to help as best as I can.</string>

    <string name="ocwAttribution">Open Source Libraries Used</string>
    <string name="ocwAttributionDesc">• Jsoup\n\t\thttps://github.com/jhy/jsoup/\n\n• Picasso\n\t\thttps://github.com/square/picasso\n\n• Gson\n\t\thttps://github.com/google/gson\n\n• InternetAvailabilityChecker\n\t\thttps://github.com/AggarwalAnkit/InternetAvailabilityChecker</string>

    <string name="videoWarning">This course has some video content which sometimes is not shown properly in the app. Be sure to check the course in any browser to make sure you are not missing out on anything.</string>
    <string name="allCoursesHints">Name, Course Code or Semester</string>

</resources>